April. It is Sunday today. And today is a very special day. That's right.
Oh no! I have to... hold on.
There. I have to print the chat before I can see it.
Also, uh... Bonnie Wynn. Welcome to the circle. I don't think I've seen you in the chat before,
but welcome. Good to see you. Thank you. Supo or XYpo. Let me know which pronunciation is correct here.
With five pounds and joining the potato. Welcome. Welcome. How do I pronounce your name correctly?
I feel like I prefer XYpo, but I can... I will respect if it's different.
Printer restored.
Hey there, Oliver. Hey, uh, I can't pronounce your name because it's made of Cyrillic characters.
Good to see you.
Suipo? Suipo. Okay. Unless I also fuck that one up. Thanks. Suipo. Thank you.
Ha ha ha. Didn't watch the video. Now I don't get the newest chat joke.
I feel like we have way too many internal jokes going on here.
Or maybe we have the right amount. I'm not quite sure. I'm torn.
Typing extra long chat messages. Don't mind me. I'm just wasting your printer ink.
Speaking of extra long chat messages, uh, hopefully the chat should be fixed today and
some people suggested in the comments on the live stream that the chat was also a little bit too small.
So I increased this general size of it, just a tad.
I also reduced any opacity on it, so it should be a little easier to read on lower resolutions as well.
Hopefully it's good. We'll see.
So the plan today is I'm gonna be streaming for about, I think, three hours.
Approximately. Maybe a little bit more.
I have some plans after that. So, yeah, that's the plan for today.
I don't even remember... Hold on, let me actually quickly close chat down.
I will see you guys on the other side.
Play and play. Kind of weird that I have to click play twice.
Well, yeah. Okay. Let's see here. What was I even doing?
Oh, right. Wait, I also have my noisy keyboard right now. Let me just quickly
get rid of that so you don't have to listen to the
tippity tap. It's a keyboard that I absolutely need when I play Starcraft. So
let's see here.
There we go. Hopefully it's working. It's working!
And dude! Some shit happened last time, huh? Check this out.
I have an unpleasant meatball. It's very unpleasant.
And then I have an undertaker with over 9,000 bullets. So that's so nice.
I have a sick pickaxe. And I have an artery. And I'm so ready to punish
fiends, demons, monsters and old men alike. Today shall be a crazy day.
What was I even doing last time? Why did I...
Why did I go this way? I think... Oh, actually, I think I do remember. I prepared for adventure.
Did I lose some... I think I may have died.
Oh, wait, I remember, I think. Yeah, yeah, I died and lost... Yeah.
I think I had some money on me that I lost. I was in the cave to the west.
Unless I remember wrong.
Okay, so let me check the map real quick.
I want to go here. I want to go back here because that's where I died.
I was fighting a brain right here. I remember this now.
And I lost. It was not a good time. I mean, it was a good time, but you know what I mean.
I may have been murdered. Also, we need Abigail, I just realized.
Let me do the... Oh, wait, how did I just...
Oh, wait, I think I just did some kind of crazy move there.
Um, Michelinius.
There we go. Also, my inventory.
Do I really need all of this? I don't need bottles of water on me.
I do need these, though.
Boulder, I want to bring because I want to experiment.
Torches are good to have. In fact, I'll put them here.
And maybe I'll replace
uh, this one for now. I guess I can put the fishing pole in here for now. I don't need it right now.
Yeah, that's good. Recall potion is good to have. Scarab bomb. I'll take it.
Gel, go in. Mushroom stays. I have 240 HP and a cellar's harpoon. I have lots of stuff. Let's go.
It is time for adventure. I'm actually so excited. I will kill that damn brain.
And I will also try to uh, summon the eye again. I guess I need to test something regarding that.
Look at this. The zombie has a gel on his head, on his head. Speaking of eyes, get out of here.
Well, this is a green eye. Maybe I should just yo-yo these guys.
The yolo is actually a little bit annoying. Let me try the spear here.
Spear is pretty cool. I can dig the spear. Let me see here. Yeah, the range is very nice.
Definitely very nice to keep enemies at bay.
Get some practice here with these weapons.
Also, I kind of forgot if I had these weapons last time I fought the brain or if I got these after.
I don't remember. We're almost there. Oh, I'm gonna take this. Give me that mushroom.
Also, we got to find the bonifish. It's very important. Come here.
Nice. Uh, it was not here, was it? Oh, it was here. Never mind. It was here.
I gotta say, man, the maze here is- it's still so good. I may just keep using it.
Go here.
This thing right here is annoying me. Oh, man, it feels good to be back in this game.
It's a nice game, isn't it? I'm just gonna grab this while I'm here.
What if I take some of this blood water with me in a bucket?
I wonder what I can use it for. Get out of here.
Okay, let's place torches.
Oh, yeah, I have this now. Which one was it? This one. Quick climbing claws.
Slide down walls. Super nice. Let me go a little faster here. Oh, wait, I can do this.
Yeah. Oh, careful. That does so nicely against those torches.
Do I not have a light anymore on me? Come on. Oh, I do have the mining helmet on.
That's nice. I wonder if I should maybe replace that.
Because, I mean, I don't really need the light.
But it's nice to have, I guess. I mean, I have torches.
Where did I die? Oh, I think I died up there.
Torches need light. Is that my money? Yeah, this is where I fought.
But then I... Hold on. Did I go back, recover my money, and then recall?
It's very possible. I can't believe I don't remember this.
Ah, we've got more of those hearts. Get out of here. Get in there.
Wait, I need to use the hammer here. Wait, there we go.
A horrible chill goes down your spine. Yeah, I think...
I think this is bad. I think it's about to happen again. So let's get ready.
Let's get mega ready here. Same position as last time. Iron skin.
What else? What else do I need? Maybe grenades. Let's have a grenade on us.
Come on. Okay, there's a lot of enemies here. Let's just get rid of these first.
Also, I want to make a little bit of extra room here. Let me just go like that.
So I have some more room. Like that. Oh, I don't like the water here, though.
Ah, that's fine. Oh, we've got to clean up these fucking guys.
So step... first phase is easy. That's just... I just have to spin to win. Come on.
Let me put down some light so I can see what I'm doing. When is it coming? Brain.
Show thyself. Oh, god. I need to eat this.
How much armor do I have right now? 27. Didn't I have a statue? Oh, did I not bring that?
Oh, I should have brought a statue.
That's a mistake on my part here. Crap. What about my extra nice food? Oh, I should have brought food
as well. I'm such a dummy. Also, this thing is not appearing. Maybe I remember wrong.
Maybe it's not going to appear right now. Oh, my god. Get away from me, please.
Now, it doesn't seem like it's coming. Why are there so many enemies?
Hold on. Get through this.
Feels so good to be able to finally do this. I also have to test this pickaxe in general on
normal ass like stone. Oh, yeah, it's so good. It's so good. Okay, I just want to go down here.
Abigail is just fighting monsters all the time. That's fine with me. Drain all this water.
Wait, what? Get out of here. Okay, no monster so far. Interesting.
Didn't I have some... Oh, yeah, these I want to try actually.
Oh, R. All right, they sort of do that. Can I extend this hook while I'm on it somehow?
Just that dirt.
Wait. Invisibility potions.
Why is that just here? Randomly on the floor, isn't that weird? Look at that. There's a guy over there.
Skeleton. I'm gonna dig my way into him and fuck him up. Dude, I love caving.
That's maybe one of my favorite parts about this game so far. It's just
forgot. Going caving feels so good. Why am I stuck here? I can't move.
Oh, that was weird. I was stuck. Grab the amethyst. Excuse me, Mr. Skeleton.
I think he senses me. Silly boy. Rope and some silver. Oh, there's a heart over there.
I will take that. Stick to the right. Actually, I have an idea.
Directed explosion. Oh, that's so good! Love it!
Screams echo around you. Okay, I think this is it. This is it. Get to position.
Come on. Up, up, up, up, up, up. Come on.
Yeah, that's fine. Here we go.
There we go. Get out of here.
Okay, here we go. This has to be it. Get rid of that shit. Get rid of the evidence.
Nothing happened here. Nothing happened. We need low lights. We need to have a party!
Rave! And then we also need this. Let's put it here. I need to stay in range of the cozy fire.
Let's see when it goes away. Oh, it has quite a range. That's nice.
Oh, come on. Bloodcrawler banner!
Hey, that's kind of nice, isn't it? Do I have that already?
Bloodcrawler... I don't. Oh, that's amazing for this.
Oh, the damage increase! It's significant.
Why is the bomb not coming? Maybe it's not yet. What the fuck? Do I have terrible memory?
What is up here? Get away from me. I'm gonna go up here. What do we got?
Just a little area.
Aha! Dude, I think the scarab bombs are my favorite of the bombs so far. It's so fucking cool.
What? Hold on, actually. Delete these fuckers. I don't want them.
I need to keep my inventory completely organized. Today is the day of organized inventory.
And of course, no deaths. But that goes without saying.
We shall not die today. This will be a deathless stream.
Mark my words. I know there are non-believers out there.
I'm here to dispel your non-belief and make you a believer. Grab all this.
And then we have a monster. Let me spear these fuckers. I mean, the spear is...
It's okay. It's not the best. Oh, god. Okay, nice. Dude, my pink... my... what is it? My pinky toe?
My little... the smallest toe I have on my foot. I think I broke it.
I walked into something after coming home from the store today and it hurt like a mother fucker
and it's still hurting whenever I touch it. I hope it's okay. So if I actually... what I'm trying
to say here is, if I end up dying, it's because of that. It's not my fault. It's the little toe.
The pinky toe. Okay, so that's explored. Let's go left now. Got a little bit of a...
hole here. Oh, what was that? How did I just propel my... it wasn't this... oh, was it actually?
Maybe it was. Never mind. I'm imagining things. What is that up there? Oh.
Is that really it down here? Actually, no, there's more over here. I didn't see that.
Where is this? And then... does we have so many bombs anyway? Let's just bomb the shit out of this place.
Dude, bombs are actually fucking satisfying. Just bomb the shit out of everything. Oh, god, here we go.
Here we go. There you go. You're dead. Take care of this face monster. And now we got to go
down one level. Uh, yep. Everything's fine. I hate those guys so much.
More bombs. Lovely. Actually, I do want that on my thing up here. Yeah, you know what? Fuck this
spear for now. The spear is not that great. Here's another one. Actually, you know what?
This makes sense. I think it's the rule of three here. So I have an idea, actually. Before I break
this, I'm actually gonna go home first. I have so many of these anyway. I'm gonna go home. I'm gonna
empty my inventory. I'm gonna clean my inventory. And I'm gonna bring the statue. What do I have?
Put this in here. I don't need that right now.
Uh, can I have like a potion that increases gun damage, please? That's what I want. That's what I need.
Oh, wait. I should just click this button. Quick stack.
Actually, this could be pretty cool. I'm gonna keep that for now.
Now, this goes in the weapon chest. The boulder. This one gets deleted.
Uh, let's see.
I think that's fine. I don't know why I'm carrying all these. Put them in here.
Deposit my money as well. Oh, wait. I already did that.
Right. So when I quick stack, that also puts in the money. That makes sense.
Uh, so now I want to grab a statue. And I had one on this side as well, didn't I?
Maybe out here, actually.
Yeah, there it is. What's up? You want potion?
The monsters of the robust can have slain you 42 times already?
I wonder which one picked up your banner. Huh.
I have a banner.
Ugh. I hate how unhealthy it is to cram so many people in one place.
What? Dante the arms dealer? I don't have a crush. I don't. Shut up.
I don't like Rosalva to dry it that much. Kind of weirds me out.
I feel like you may have a crush on Dante the arms dealer, ma'am.
Call it a sixth sense.
Psst. Might have a job for you. I don't think you can say no either.
Oh yeah. A new one? It's a whale. It's a dolphin. No, it's a penguin fish.
Oh, and look, it's you. You get to bring me one. You do know the only, like, cold water, right?
God in surface tundra. Pinkfish.
Pinkfish. All right, man. I gotcha. So statue has been acquired.
And then we also need... What else can I actually make? I need to... Okay, so if we're
gonna prepare for battle here, let's prepare for battle. Let's take some bottles.
Let's take this as well.
Let's see here. Haley. Stop pulling on my tail, bro. It's totally real and, like, totally hurts
when you pull on it. All right. Whatever. Hanno? No, you have clothes. Dylan, tell me once again.
I once again ask you what the requirements are to make these damn potions.
Oh, wait. No, no, no. I remember now. I remember it needs organics.
I needed to make something.
Let's just grab a couple things here. Maybe that, actually. And that, that...
It's gonna be hell for me to remember these recipes. What the fuck?
Vicious mushroom. Let's try this one. And...
Yes, sure. That's fine. Actually, the seeds are kind of useless, right? Okay, let's see here.
What can we make? We can make... Vicious powder.
Wait. Why isn't...
No, no, no. Crafting? This one?
Yellow dye? This one? I guess teal dye, yeah. Okay, what about this?
Butterfly statue? No. Vicious moth room?
Shiverthorn? Oh, here we go. Oh, wait, I can't make that.
Let's just move swiftly in liquids. Water leaf. Oh, wait, I can actually make this.
Allow you to see nearby danger sources.
Oh, that sounds like something that is very interesting to me.
Cobweb. Don't I have that?
Maybe not. Organics? Cobweb. Perfect. Now, bro, tell me exactly what I need to craft it.
Um... this one? No, what was it again? What was it? I forgot.
What did I just put in? I'm losing my mind. This one. Right. And then...
What's this? Increases knockback? Increases placement speed and range. Oh!
That's pretty nice. I want to make this. Just requires a bottle. Yes!
Make three of these. That's cool. I guess it will reveal boulders and shit.
So I don't die to that anymore. I've had so many deaths to those fucking things.
Okay. And now? I need something that buffs me, though. Something that will... what about this
sand gun? Mining potion. Blink root and lion mandible.
Wait, I can... illegal gun parts? Banned in most places.
Hmm. Also, I want to make some better armor as well now that I'm at it.
So what is the best I have?
Crimtane. Platinum. Tongsten.
Let's... maybe... Give me that.
First off, we make some bars. Okay, that's only one. That's fine. And then...
here. Let's see. Oh, I can make platinum, actually. I didn't even... Okay, okay, nice.
But I don't have enough to make...
any... um... whatchamacallit...
crimtane things. Wait, I can make this? Hey, let's just have... let's just buff this shit up.
Let's have a shit ton of monster lasagna. Tastes like hairs and meats with noodle.
I hate that. That's very unfortunate.
Oh, this is a way better defensive helmet, actually.
Let's do it. And then I also want to make...
Oh, wait, that's it? I thought I had way more platinum. Did I really not have more platinum?
That's almost unbelievable. Oh, wait, I have. Nice.
Platinum. Make it all. Stack it. And then I want to make...
um... let's see.
Oh, I don't have enough to make a chest or boots, I don't think.
Lead. No, that sucks. Create. Okay. But this is a good upgrade for now.
Yeah. Let me grab these. And grab that. And those... man, there's so many of these goddamn stars.
What else should I make while I can? If I can make better bullets, actually,
I should probably do it, because I'm gonna be shooting my gun.
What is the best bullet I can make? Unholy arrow.
Hold on. Hey, you there, Dylan. Tell me about the normal musket bullets again.
What is... how much does this do? Nine.
Cursed bullet requires cursed flame. Iker. Yeah, I don't have that.
Chases after your enemy? Dude!
That seems insane.
Wow. Okay. Well, well, well, well. Oh, wait, I also have things here. Hold on a sec now.
You know what? Sometimes it may be a good idea to just take everything and just walk over here
and see what I can craft. Maybe that's the better way of checking these things.
Like right now, I know I can craft this.
Danger sources, night vision, or of light.
Yo, hold on. Let's do this one. What is... oh, that's plastic. Sure, throw it away for now.
I'll put it there and then make more healing potions. Better ones. There we go. And then also,
I guess I can make this to...
Oh, that's max. Okay, gotcha. Oops. I should have probably tested that before I made so many.
Whoops. Ludo. Try swirly pink and purple. It works, I swear.
How about I sell you something instead, huh? Would you like some? Actually, never mind.
Mana crystals are material. I can maybe craft something with it. Let me quickly check with Dylan.
Band of star power. Oh, requires a panic necklace. Okay, sure. Okay, for now, just put all the
organics. Oh, this is going to be hell, isn't it?
Inventory management. Not my strong suit. Sort. Tissue sample.
This one, that one. This one. That's an... that's armor. Wait, do I have an armor
thingy? Oh, wait, wait, wait. Blood crawler, molten legion, diabolic. Let me take that
and that one. Maybe they will help me in that fight. What else could possibly help?
Marching bones. I'm not sure. That's like the closest I can think of relating to that brain.
What else do I have here? Breathe water instead of... Oh, I have these here! What the fuck?
I didn't even know. My goodness. That's so important. Zombie banner. Put that in here as well.
Oh, god damn. That's awesome. Bloody tears. Someone's the blood moon.
Yeah, I don't know about that, dude.
Maintain strange symbols. Okay, let's deposit some stuff. You go in here. You go in there.
I should have like a chest for armor and stuff.
And equipment. Equipment chest.
You know, for now it's Michelinius, but I'm gonna organize that later. This also goes in here.
And we have the mushrooms. Okay, this looks sort of good. I think. Sort.
A golden key. I want to bring that just in case I encounter a chest that I can use it on.
Okay, I think we're ready.
I think we are ready. So I have 27 defense now, and that's without any buffs.
What is with all these stars? There's so many of them. I guess I can use them to make...
Did you see that? Is something down here?
That was a magic thing. Like little... almost looked like the fairy.
Is it trying to tell me something?
Ships in the traveling merchant. You know what? Let's quickly check that out.
Let's check that out. Maybe he has some sick items.
Ow! Stupid target dummy.
Ship turn! You look like a well-traveled man.
Meet me behind Dylan's house in about three hours. I think I have something you will find very
appealing. See, now is the time I would like to have a watch so I can know exactly when the
fuck that is. Sake. Lord... what? Fedora? Tips? Milady?
There was a counterweight after hitting an enemy with a yo-yo?
Displace the name of rare creatures around you. I want all of this. Just... I mean, I have the
money. Give me that. Give me that. This one seems shit.
Let's... hmm... This one seems kind of crazy. I don't know what it means, but I'll take it.
Let me see here. There was a counterweight after hitting an enemy with a yo-yo?
Hold on. What do I have right now? This one?
Three defense. Sure, let's exchange this one for now. Let's test this out. There was a counterweight.
What the fuck does that mean? Like an extra damage type thing? Is that gonna damage?
Oh yeah, I think... Hold on, let's see. Oh yeah, I think it is hitting it. It's doing more damage, right?
Yeah, I'm honestly not sure. Life form analyzer? Let's see what this does.
Oh shit. Wait. Wait, is it raining slimes right now?
Yeah, I don't care for the raining slimes. I'm gonna go. I'm going.
Ah, I'm going. I'm gonna be so buffed. Yo, it's gonna be insane here. What else did I get? A water gun.
Wait, does it actually...? Maybe I can turn something... Maybe I can change something with it.
Wait, it's definitely not doing damage. I didn't expect it to, but maybe it has like some effect
where you can turn something that is made of fire into water or like make it less dangerous or something.
You know what I mean? I'll have to see. I'm gonna put this back for now. Get away from me.
Get away from me, sir. I need to take a sip. Oh yeah. I also want to check what's down here
all the way at the bottom. This looked very interesting by the way. I think I'll go there next.
And check it out.
Okay, we have arrived. Tisted dungeon. This thing is not doing anything yet, but it does say rare creatures.
So, I guess I'll know when I see it. Okay, so here's the plan. First, we light up the place.
What's this? Oh, why is it there?
Uh, let me grab the cozy fire.
And these. And this one. I'm gonna put it more in the center, so I'm assured that I am in range of it.
Let's do like... I want to hang it here. Get away from me.
Stupid asshole. I guess this also serves to block off the creatures below me
while this is happening.
Okay, let's see if one of these work. Slime is kind of useless here.
Maybe I want this right now. It gives me movement speed. That can't hurt. Oh god, I didn't even see
you there. You bastard. Okay, eat this. Eat this. Let's see. Oh, right, life regeneration. Okay.
And then, will they stack? They will stack. Look at that.
And then this. Oh, we are buffed. And also, I'm gonna put this here.
Nice. And that's pretty much it, right? Wait, we also... Oh, wait, wait, wait.
We have more banners.
Now we're fucking ready. Let me block this shit off. Ah, fuck. Next time.
Dude, the damage I do now. Here we go.
Oh, yeah. There it is. Awoken.
Block it off. Oh, shit. Oh, scheisse.
Okay, this is actually kind of nice. Oh, wait, I have the wrong weapon.
Fucking, just get rid of these first. I gotta heal.
Okay, here's the thing though. Oh, here's the mega brain play.
I'm gonna wait a bit in this phase to wait for my potion to regen
before I get to the next stage here. I'm just gonna kite it a little bit.
This is gigabrain in action. Watch me min-max the shit out of this.
Oh, god. Oh, god. Yeah! Oh, shit.
Okay, I'm actually still taking damage, but that's actually kind of not the point.
Maybe I can shoot as well. Okay, don't go too far in here.
Get back up. Oh, no, not spiders. Not now. Oh, is he going into mega crazy mode now?
Or maybe a... Hold on. Is he invisible?
No, he's up there. Hold on. I wonder if I can drink this and make a show of the location of
enemies. Can I see him? Let's get... Oh! Oh, he teleports around. I see.
Oh, wait. I think he's immune to damage in this phase. Let me regen a bit before I kill the remaining.
I'm re-genning. Yep, here we go. Kill it. Here we go. Okay, get out of there.
Oh, I'm so slow. Shoot it with guns. Oh, shit.
Oh, okay. I see, I see. It's only the really red one that's dangerous.
Yeah, okay, okay, okay. I understand, I understand, I think. Just shoot it down. Oh my god.
Okay, the gun is better. Which one is the real one?
It's a heal. Don't die now. Bro, I'm spamming the heal button. Come on. Which one is the real one?
Yes! Oh, yeah. Let's see. Treasure bag, brain of Catullu.
And crimtane ore, a lot of it too. Hold on, let me clear these first.
Do not disturb me while I look in my treasure bag. Let me actually...
Don't annoy me while I'm doing this. Okay, let's see. Brain of confusion.
Has a chance to create illusions and dodge and attack.
Temporarily increases critical chance after dodge,
may confuse nearby enemies after being struck.
Wait a minute. There's a chance to create illusions and dodge and attack.
Temporarily increases critical chance after dodge.
Hell yeah, dude.
So that means like a passive avoidance thingy? Like there's a chance not to take damage?
That sounds pretty neat, honestly.
Wait, bone rattle? Someone's a babyface monster.
Oh, equipable. Wait a minute.
Oh, wait. Ah, look. It's here now.
Is it going to protect me in combat though, or is it just like a cute little thingy? That's the question.
Um, that's pretty cool, dude. I freaking did it. Now there's also a way down here.
Let me do that. We're gonna keep going, man. With all these buffs we have, we gotta...
Oh, he's confused. Yep, there it is.
In fact, I'm gonna go up here and grab my banners again.
Thanks. Oh, my inventory is full.
That was awesome, though. The gun came in clutch there. Look at all the spiders.
Okay, there's two paths. I'm gonna take left. Okay, now we're back down here.
Sure, dig through it. Fuck off. Oh, wait a minute.
I'm gonna do this now.
Oh, wait. No, no, that's not what I meant to do. Ah, shit. Wrong button. Oh, well.
It is what it is.
Affordable chill goes down your spine. Does that mean I can keep... Oh, my god, it's dark.
Open it up. Drain the shit out of this place.
Can I just keep summoning that thing?
What's happening? Oh, it's a salamander. It's so dark. I need my mining helmet, dude.
Mining helmet is fucking amazing. They're so confused all the time. This is great.
What's that? Is that a slime statue? It is. Sure, just put it back, I guess. I don't want that.
Uh, the boulder... Wait, what? Sorry, what now? What is that red stuff?
Hey, I don't get it. I mean, I can... Can I not dislodge it? Okay, interesting.
I have no idea what that just was. Okay, I'm gonna go into this cave up here now.
And I'm gonna utilize the special thingy for that.
I need to do that first. Then I use this.
Oh! No! The wrong button, damn it!
Shit! God damn it, I hate when I press the wrong button. Slime has stopped falling from the
sky. Okay, that's about time. Let's not die here. Look at them, they're all confused.
Wait a minute, is this... Look at how the... I didn't even realize this thing did that.
When I hit it at an angle, it sort of bounces off. Look, I had no idea I could do that with this.
That's awesome. Uh, wait, we have constructions there. Get out of here.
Okay, now I'm back in this cave I was in earlier.
I feel like it's been ages since I was in here. Nice. I want all of this and I want to put that
there. I'm definitely gonna bring my mining helmet next time. Or actually, I don't have a potion for
light. Uh, maybe not. Also put a... That looks pretty cool actually.
Um, is this thing flying with...
with a crime mirror? The hell, man. That's kind of dope. Unlike your style.
This looks boring. Nothing up there. I'm gonna go down further down.
And I will use nearby danger sources. Oh, that's danger source.
Why is that a danger source? A meteorite has landed.
Where? Can I see that? How big are we talking? Meteorite. I wonder if I can see that.
Maybe not. Maybe it's just close to where I have my house. What's that? Oh, it's just nothing.
Uh, give me this. Man, I want the treasure potion again. The one that reveals treasure.
That's... Oh, don't put an extra one. That's a waste. See, it's too dark down here, damn it.
Uh, what can I do? Wait, can I place torches underwater?
I don't think so. So, what we're gonna do? We're gonna bomb the shit out of it.
Bomb? Where are you? Fucking hell, where are you?
Wait. Violent panic necklace. Oh, I didn't even notice I got this.
Hold on a sec. 4% melee speed.
Maybe I'll replace it with that, see how big of an effect it really is. Okay, let's see.
Keep eating the monster lasagna. Generation, swiftness, iron skin.
Uh, where's my bombs? Did I use them all? I almost can't believe that. Maybe I did.
Okay, I'm gonna be digging without knowing where I'm going.
I'm just gonna hold down and hope for the best. Actually, when I'm a man, there's a cave right
here. Let me just use that. Wait, there's something down there. What's that?
Live crystal! Yo! Hold on!
My inventory sucks. Get rid of...
Uh, I don't know. Cobweb. And this. Are you actually kidding me? That was a live crystal there!
Hey! 260. Oh, man. Okay. Oh, what's... Oh, dude. I'm gonna use this here.
That's totally what they are for. What's that?
What? Found goblin? Excuse me?
Can I unbind you? Oh, wait. I'm actually dying here.
Can I drain this water? Damn it. Hold on. Let me actually make a little drainage canal here.
Drain it out. All of it. Can I drain more?
Hey. Grotex. Yo, I heard you like rockets and running boots. So, I put some rockets in your running boots.
Uh, allows flight? Hold on.
What? Why? Why were you slain?
Hello? What happened?
Why were you slain? No! He sold me flight! There's no way!
Did he drop it at least?
It doesn't look like... Oh, my God. Oh, my God. He's gonna respawn though, right?
Tell me he's gonna respawn, man. All right, fine. I'll... See, that's the danger source right there.
That's a damn danger source.
It also kind of reveals where there's another cave.
Pretty neat. No, I should go back. I don't have any inventory. Fucking hell. Let's go back.
Wait, why are we so fast?
Medium... You can send... Wait, wait, wait. Why are we this fast?
Increases movement speed after taking damage. Movement speed increased and monster spawns... I'm happy.
Huh. All right.
Well, first off, crimtane! Make it all.
Put that there for now. Let me also quickly click on this magic button. Lovely. Wait,
what did I just put in there? Annoying the Undertaker.
Nimble. Put water gun in there.
And let's cook some more things down here. Make all the bars. That's good. And now...
Take these. Fjeld. There it is. There it is.
Let me talk to him. Fjeld. Goblins are surprisingly easy to anger. In fact,
they could start a war over cloth. Reforge. Place an item to reforge.
I hope it means what I think it means. Let's test. One gold.
Another chance at stats, I guess. Forceful. Yep. Yep. Exactly what I thought.
Okay.
Can I reforge this? I can reforge these, too. Can I reforge this? Do I want to?
Precise. Shit, what did it have before? I should have checked before.
Oh, no. Why didn't I check that beforehand?
Definitely didn't have the critical strike chance. That's something I know.
Reforge. Okay, cool. Anyway, shop. Graveling hook. Tool belt. Increases block placement range by one.
That seems pretty nice. Tinkera's workshop. Allows the combining of some accessories.
Uh, yes. Thank you, ruler. Sure, let's try it. Rocket boots.
Wait, they don't go on my boots? Are you kidding? That makes no sense at all.
How does it work? Now it's flight.
Whoops.
No. Bro, what the fuck? That's insane. Okay, okay. My goodness, I'm getting all the things.
That's insane. Uh, let's me put this down somewhere.
Where can I... You know what? Let's remove this one block.
There, so that we can put this there.
Uh, allows combining of certain accessories. Wait, how does this work?
Stop! Opening and closing the door. I'm losing my mind.
Ah, fuck off door. What? Boy, that sun is hot. I do have some perfectly ventilated armor.
Am I talking to the dresser? I'm so confused. Pinwheel.
Wait a minute. The sun is high, but my prices are not?
I'm so confused. I hate how many people hang around, but none of them buy anything.
Wait, am I clicking on this guy?
I like the scenery in the forest. A good view attracts customers.
Lion Pines the golfer makes loads of money. I like deep pockets.
Catlin the nurse makes loads of money. I like deep pockets.
I hate easy the angler's terrible personality. Bro, say it like it is.
I think it's because I had that function activated. How does this work?
Why is this not? Ah, wait a minute. Let me just take a couple of these.
Can I do something now? I don't get it. I don't understand this fucking item.
Okay, whatever. Put some stuff in here.
All the accessories. Then we can have all the banners in there. Make some nice... oops, that's not a banner.
Potions, I think it's good to have on you. Did I put this in there?
A door? Let's put it back. There we go.
Now, crimtane! Blink root seeds. Uh, crimtane. Definitely do like the crimtane.
The question is though, I think I definitely want to make this. But, hold on. Hold on.
There was also another thing regarding
samples of tissue.
Where is it?
The inventory management. There it is. Ah, here we go.
I should make armor. I should make armor, dude. How much is this? Oops, not that one.
25? What is this? Six defense? This is... oh, that's a big upgrade.
This is seven defense. Five boots are a better upgrade.
I'm making all of it. I'm crazy. I know. I don't care. We're going full BDE.
Look at that, dude. Let me pull off this. Oh yeah, look at me. I look like a true warrior.
Put this on the stand.
Hang out my hat after a long day at work. Very nice. This one I bring with me.
Okay, let's put our armor up here. This is the armor and weapons. This is the
anything you can wear, sort of thing. Chest.
Nice. And then this one goes in.
Also, my question now is, do we really need the double jump?
Actually, I do. Plus three defense. That's pretty sick. This one, though, I don't know about that.
Maybe I will prefer
this one. Plus three defense. Look at me. 33 defense right now with no buffs.
And a violent panic necklace. That one could be used, right?
To do this one. No, this one. What is this? Releases bees. It houses the user in honey
and increases movement speed when damaged. What the fuck? Who comes up with this?
Well, all right. That's very weird. Sure. Tissue sample, Dylan. Look at this.
Ooh, hold on. Increases summon damage. Right, what was this?
Void bag. Summons the void vault. Functions as an extended inventory when open.
May pick up overflowing items when open. This seems insane.
I want this. I want this real bad.
Void vault. Stored items can only be accessed by you or contained items picked up by a void bag.
Bro. I need to get to the jungle and gain jungle spores and then I need to find bones.
Probably from skeletons, I would imagine.
Uh, right.
You know what I should do? I should place a chest right next to the...
I should make like a potion crafting station where I put all the ingredients for potions there.
You know? Also, hold on. Let me talk to Rosalva.
What's this about me having more bark than bite? Good one.
What's the status? The robust can is 6% crimson. So that hasn't changed, huh? All right.
Uh, I kind of want to buy some of this again to test because I didn't...
I feel like I didn't test that properly. Uh, what's this?
Dirt rod.
Let's buy some of this. Yeah. Let's make a garden here.
Let me try this. See how that works. So what if I just...
So that just works like that, huh? Okay. Cool.
Um...
Hmm. I feel like...
I kind of want to build a house close to the ocean.
Just because I can... I want to go fish so often. And it's just such a long way there.
Also want to go back down there. What's over here?
This is where the old man is.
I feel like this place has to be special as well because there's these two trees here.
What does it say? Living wood. Oh, it actually...
Oh, wait, what? Wow, it actually reveals...
If I mouse over it says platinum.
Oh, cool. I didn't know that. That's pretty neat.
Um, all right. Let me try this weapon real quick.
Because apparently this is a weapon.
All right. It probably has extremely fast attack. Yeah, very fast speed.
What are they talking about? Here. You guys can't see anything.
And now you shall see. Let me put the ruler in my chest for now.
Um, detect enemies around you. No. Man, I need more slots here. I feel like this is not enough.
I want more. Man, I am upgraded. What should I do now? I think I want to go down to a dungeon again.
I think I know which one too. No, no, actually I want to plant.
Let's make a little... Do I do this outside or what? What is this buff from?
The Bass Defense. Ah, look, these are all the stacks from these three there.
The Babyface Monster is following you. I don't know if I want that to be following me honestly.
Uh, someone's a hard to...
Get rid of this. I don't like that. Makes me uneasy. Put it in here.
Okay. The rest of the stuff? I think Rootsy... oops, no.
Gelanius. Panic Necklace going here.
What's this? Oh, I thought something happened to the Spiky Bowl because of the background green
moon there or whatever that is. That just confused me. This one is good to have. The key I'll keep.
Man, there's so many items. I feel like I need to carry on around all the time.
Actually, maybe I don't need the Artery. These two I want to keep. These are like my main men.
Put this one in there. I'm gonna be more deliberate now with what I bring. Let me place this inside
somewhere. And let me also make some platforms. Do I have that? Not on me right now, but I can
make a bunch. I think it's good to have anyway. In fact, this may even be better to use in the dungeons
instead of just the dirt, because I can actually go through it, right?
So, and the enemies can't. I don't think so. It's only to my advantage to use that
anywhere I go, so always keep that on me. Go like this now, and then we're gonna make...
Yes, look at that. Actually, move it one up, because that way I can...
Oh wait, no, that's not enough room. Never mind. Okay, never mind. This is fine.
That's good. And then we fill it up with this. And then we have Blink thingies. Blink root.
Oh wait, this is not the seed. Do I have that?
Mush... Sword.
Ligro seeds. I wonder if I can get seeds from... What if I... Wait, plants are just growing.
Whoa. Why doesn't that work? Ah, no, not again! Oh, that system sucks.
When you put it, if you accidentally double click, it attacks right after and destroys it.
That's so stupid! Fuck! God damn it!
All right, fine. Keep your secrets. What about the crimson? Didn't I also have another planter?
Where did that go? Deathweed, right.
Deathweed. I think I have that.
Deathweed. There we go. Let's keep that on the other side here.
And then let's be careful. Oh wait, this is not a seed.
Fuck. Do I have seeds? Shit, I don't think I do. God damn it!
Man, this... Farming is above me apparently. I can't do it. It's too difficult. My brain cannot comprehend
how this works. Uh, let's go. Actually, now I want to try something.
Because now it is night and I have a theory that... Uh, where is it?
Yep! There it is. Oh shit. I might... I should have prepared maybe. Come here. Come here, fucker.
I just want to see if he still drops sick items.
Oh wait, I can fucking fly now.
Haha! This is good practice. Yeah, dude! Oh god, let's not... let's calm down a bit here.
Heck yeah, dude. Oh, I take a lot of damage from falling. Oh shit. Okay, move!
All right, he does that shit. Come on.
Yep. Bring it on.
I'm farming this guy right now. Oh, be careful. There it is. Actually, we do!
We got another bag! Ha!
Crimson seeds. Hey, this is a way to get crimtane! Bro, we're doing it again. I don't even care. We're
doing it again. Come on, come on. Okay, I'm practicing with the flying here.
I can sort of use a little bit at a time. That's actually a big discovery. Where'd it go?
Oh, it's because it's morning! Ah, crap! Fuck! Haha! Whoops. Okay, it's okay. Let me put some stuff in
chest and then we go out again. Uh, crim... let's make it into bars. I wonder how I get more of
those that I can summon then. I kind of forgot where I got it. Shield of Cthulhu.
Two percent critical strike. Wait, six? Oh, it's the same. This one is better.
Okay. All right, well, put it in here for now.
Mechanics, that goes in. Uh, actually. Put it there.
And the construction in here. Seats there.
Would... bring this, actually. Bring it with me. Danger sense. Okay, then.
Let's bring some glow sticks in case we need it.
Bahum fish? Yeah, sure, why not? May as well use it.
All right, people, I'm off. See you later. But look at me now. I'm full of armor. Oh, wait,
wait, wait. I need the statue. What's this? Why do I have that on me? I should remove that.
Oh, should I bring my...
We gotta find fish! So I'm gonna craft something very special.
Flash catcher. Yeah. And where's the... there. You go there. Let's bring some bait.
What do we got? 25%. Yeah. Why the hell not? Cool. Let's move.
Okay, man. We are on top of everything right now.
So where am I going now? So I have two quests now, actually.
Wait a minute. Look at this!
I don't know why I think that's so... oh, wait, there's also here.
Oh, it's like a scroll. I see now.
I want to go fish. And he needed something that is very cold. So I imagine...
Here. That. I need to fish there. And then I need to fish in a...
Where exactly do I fish?
I guess... I'm not sure, actually. I'll figure it out. Maybe I'll just keep walking left now.
Also, old man! Let's go check out the old man. Oh, but it needs to be night for that.
Maybe it'll be night by the time I get there. Otherwise, I'm gonna delve into a dungeon.
Maybe even this one. Yeah, let's continue here for now. I want to see what's down here.
Oh, I should have brought my mining helmet, fuck. But, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute. Ah, there we go. There we go. Now we have some light.
Even though it's ugly to look at and it looks like a butt.
Blink root seeds! There we go! Finally getting the things we need.
Bomb? Oh, hold on. I know where to put this here now. Yes! And then I also want...
Danger. Show me danger. Oh! Oh! Indeed, that was danger. Indeed, that was danger.
Just go down. That's a button in there. That's a mushroom. Oh, there's a house!
Whoa! I didn't mean to do it like that, but green mushroom. Cool. Skeletons. What is it with these
statues? I don't understand. Magic mirror. Gazing the mirror at to return home.
No way! Is that an infinite recall potion? Mining potion. Let's try that one.
Torch silver. Yeah, sure. Thank you. Let me bring this chandelier.
There's a button up there that is worrying me. Get rid of that.
Red pressure plate. Delete it. Delete the gel as well. Crimson torch.
So these two caves here are going to connect, I think. Do I want to do that though?
I'm not sure. I want to go further down and go this way and down here.
What's that? Oh, wait. I need to map that. Sort of mandatory.
Mouse! Cool. You come with me?
Oliver was chopped up by a caveman. Really? Nah, that's not true. Link root. That's total lie.
Oh, yeah. Danger up there. Oh, wait. Didn't I die from a boulder here?
I feel like that's how I died here. Did I loot this? Red husk.
Daybloom seeds. I think I did loot this. Yeah, I totally did.
There's actually loot down there. Oh, I've got green stuff.
Hand it over. Let's make our way into this cave.
And once again, inventory full. Let's delete things.
Rope can be deleted. And what else? Man, the mining potion really did help there just now.
Link root seeds just delete this. The wood can be deleted. This one can be deleted.
The mudlocks, cobwebs. Let's use these for fun. It just blows shit up, you know. Cool.
Whoa, wait, wait, wait. Enemies. They're confused.
Hunter potion. Shows the location of enemies.
Allows the control of gravity?
Whoa, keen maze. Can be upgraded with torches. Bro, it's nothing.
Nowhere as good as my unpleasant meatball, but I'll take it. Thank you.
Mushroom grass seeds. I'm getting all kinds of things.
Just by swinging my maze. Heart reach? What's that? Increases pickup range for life hearts.
Sure, just use it. I don't care. I'm fine.
Dude, the glowing mushroom is actually important. I need that to make healing potions.
Oh, the mining speed is insane.
Oh, this guy has a lot of HP. Damn. But the thing is, I'm not... wait, I am.
How am I regenning HP? I don't have the thing on anymore. I don't understand.
Maybe there's a random effect going on here. I don't get it. Maybe there's a native inherent
life regen. Just any time. I've actually never noticed if that's the case. Come on.
Yeah. I want to go further down. Look at that. Love it. Oh! Yeah! 280 HP. Oh, it's so good.
Good. That means so much getting that. Delete the tungsten. What's this, tin?
I mean, I'll just grab the ore, I guess. There's no reason not to.
Oh, wait. I can fly, of course. Jesus Christ. And what's this with the gravity control?
I'm tempted to try that out, you know? So many glowing mushrooms.
But the problem is if I destroy those, there's no more light.
What exactly is that down there?
Low lights for the wind? Or glow sticks? I'm about to die. What actually is that?
Oh, that's crimtane! Oh!
Wow, it just appears like that.
Interesting. Let's keep going. I want to join up with the cave on the left over here.
In fact, I have an idea. What if I just go up like this? Ah, look! A little air pocket.
Beautiful. And that's a danger over there. Spotted. No more of those deaths. I'll tell you that.
By the way, I think this is still a no-death stream.
Isn't it? I think it is!
Wait. Oh, shh. Okay, we're fine. Making out the air pocket over here.
Like that. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. That's beautiful. I'm going to free this boulder.
I'm going to do this in the best way. See ya. Wow, it rolls a long way, huh?
Keep doing it. What's that? Active thingy. I'll take it. Here we go with a big one.
Drain the cave! The blood moon is rising.
You know what? This is a good cue for me to return home anyway.
My inventory is full. Let me try the mirror.
Yeah, it's not as fast.
So in a pinch, you know, maybe not as good.
Put that there. Let's click this button.
Let's eat one of these. Oh, you motherfuckers. You want to fight, huh?
Well, welcome to the Thunderdome, bitch.
What's that sound?
Fuck off. Oh, wait. Put it here, actually. I shall protect the village.
Here they come. Fuck off.
Dude, I am so powerful. Holy shit. I can't be stopped.
Haha. The progression feels really nice. 300 zombies.
Oh, fallen star right on my face. What the hell was that just now?
Dribbler. Come here. How dare you dribble in my home.
This here community does not tolerate dribblers.
What's that? A weird ass zombie.
I can't die. This is insane. Compared to the first time this happened. Wow. I mean, this is just insanity.
You know what? Close the doors. Close these doors.
Close this door as well. Actually, hold on. There we go. Have fun over there.
I am gonna quickly check my chests.
Blink root seeds. Let's try and plant these now.
There. There. There. Don't double click. Perfect.
Bro, expert. Right. This is easy.
I am slapping. Come here. Wow, I didn't even mean to kill those. They just happened to die.
They were in range of my wrath. Nice.
Okay. Man, I kind of wish they wouldn't attack anymore right now. I need to craft things.
I need to just... Can we... Okay, you know what? We're going back to this. Block that shit.
That's fine. Now I'm gonna craft.
Okay. Let's chill while this is happening. Magic. You know what? I'm gonna make a couple chests.
I'm gonna make a bunch of chests, actually. I'm gonna fill up this room. There we go.
Chests. Where are you? Where's my... out there. Am I blind?
What do I need for a chest, damn it? Was it stone? Chest, chest, chest.
This is one issue I have with the crafting system in this game. If you don't remember the recipe,
good luck doing anything. You just have to try combinations or ask the stupid guide.
Fucking hell, Dylan. How do I make a chest? Tell me. Any iron bar? Okay, gotcha.
Iron, iron, iron. Uh, so that means lead.
Thanks. Okay. How many do I need? One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. Let's make seven chests.
There we go. And now, plop, plop, plop, plop, plop, plop, plop. Amazing. Look at that.
It's not... you know what? Remove this for now. We need one more chest.
Just one more. Chest, chest, chest, chest, chest. Am I fucking blind?
Always over here. Okay, let's see. I should have made different chests, uh, types for different items.
You know what? I'm gonna spend some time doing that now, actually. So, organics or construction.
Let's see here. Oh, never mind. I don't actually have... I was about to say living wood.
But I don't really have that. It seems... unless it's in some random chest here.
Sort items. Wait, take these out and put them in here. Organics. Sort those. Sort those.
Bores and doors. Wait, sand block? No. No, put that in construction. Yeah, that's better.
Pink vase. Let's put that somewhere. Put it there. Red husk.
Piggy bank can go... You know what? Let's put the piggy bank.
Can I put that onto... Oh, nice. That's so awesome. Wait, was this intrepid chart tooth necklace?
Increases armor penetration by five. That seems really good, I guess. I mean,
this one gives me four defense. I'm gonna try this. Yeah, replace that for now.
Put this in here. Mushroom grass seeds. Can I put this in these even though it's not meant for it?
No. Okay, that's kind of good to know. It's kind of nice that it grows some flowers,
even though you don't put anything in. Looks nice. Mouse. Construction.
Man, I wish that when you craft things, it would take the things in your chests into consideration,
instead of having to have it in your inventory. That would be the biggest lifesaver for me.
Because this is gonna cost me so much trouble later on. And that's so true, man. I know it's gonna
put the recalls in here, because I have a magic mirror now.
Green mushroom. And here. Do I not have any more bombs? I feel like I had a shitton.
Why did I get all those bombs early on? I had so many bombs. Okay,
I think we are about ready to do things again. Sharp tongues, the next.
Renates. Then there. Okay, I definitely want to create chests, different styles of chests for
inventory. Otherwise, I have to mouse over and I cannot remember. Or it's too much work.
But if I have like a living chest, easy. That's organics, you know.
And golden chests, valuables. Stuff like that. That's my long-term goal with those.
So yeah. And speaking of living, you know what? Let's make it a mission to go here now anyway
and grab some living wood. Let's just do that.
Fuck you! I hate this target dummy. The target dummy shall be here.
There you go. Have fun with that.
Have fun with the dummy! Don't do anything I wouldn't.
Okay. Another day, another mission. I have a whole gang behind me.
That took a bit too much.
By the way, using this, I should have done that against the brain. It just occurred to me.
That would be one way to get out of that tricky situation where they surround you.
I really should have thought of that. Also, hold on. I gotta try this.
Wait, what? Press up to...
What? Oh! What?
See you guys! I'm falling! Oh shit.
Where am I right now?
Hello? Harpy? I almost died just now. Where the fuck did I just arrive?
What the fuck? There's an island in the sky. Look! Constellation. Clouts?
Yo! What? Lucky horseshoe? Naked fall damage? Bro. That seems pretty good.
I gotta be honest here. The brain of confusion. I don't know if I like it.
I'm gonna remove it for now. It seems like such a big thing though.
Maybe I should have it, but it just doesn't seem that good.
Put that in there. Actually, let me remove the rope. I don't like it.
What's this? Sun banner. Skyware.
World banner. Gravity banner.
Yo! I'm taking this. I'm sorry, but I'm taking this with me.
I kinda wanna use it. I kinda wanna use it, bro. I'm gonna make a specialized room just for me.
Don't hate. And I'm gonna make this chest that I got here reserved for valuables, I think.
Sunplate. Give it to me. And can I just... where's my hammer?
Whoops. Nope. Uh, hold on. Put the hammer here.
Yeah! Disc wall! Bro. Okay, okay, okay, okay.
That slide just got obliterated.
Wait, this is a bit slow. Maybe I need a better hammer. I should make a crimtane hammer.
I believe I can do it too. Is that just glass? It's just normal glass.
So what is that? What is this right here? Oh, hold on. I'm gonna grab it after.
What the fuck, dude? That's just an island in the sky. That thing is just dying automatically.
Okay, go on top now. Oh, wait, I can't. Uh, ah, smart. What even is this thing I'm attached to?
This may seem a little crazy what I'm doing here, but I don't know, man. How often do you, uh,
find this, right? I'm bringing this home, dude.
Dude. What is that? Sunplate block. Okay. There we go. Disassembled.
Inventory already full. Wow. Jesus. Uh, Feather. Lead that.
Okay, what is that? Is that platinum? I'm taking it.
Taking this whole, wait, there's actually something up here as well.
Throw that gravity thing. Insane. The whole world just turns upside down. That is a really cool effect.
What should I remove?
Maybe this. I don't want that. So, uh, the best thing is I can get down easy now,
because look negates fall damage. Is this cloud? Okay.
Cloud wall. Whoa, what's happening here? Harpies.
Bring it on, people. Shoot them down. Shoot them out of the sky.
They dropped feathers. Let's get them.
Actually, I could have negated fall damage anyway, because I have this and that.
So, you know what? I don't need to have this on me, actually. I just realized. Just put this back.
Oh, hell yeah. Let's go back. Nice. I do wonder if I can change the location where I appear.
Somehow.
Quick press this button, the magic button. And now we're gonna have a special room.
One of these chests up here. I say this one. It's gonna be a special chest. A special people.
And then we're gonna have a special table somewhere.
Let's make this a special table. Look at that.
There. What do you think of that, dude? You like it? Oh, that's a door.
It's a little bit... a little bit of everything right now, I guess.
This whole house is a mixing pot of whatever.
Let's just put down some banners. That's a door.
Where's my banners? World banner. I wonder what that does.
Okay, let's put this stuff in construction.
Ah, I forgot this on banner. That's okay.
You go in here.
Dylan, tell me about these feathers, huh? Oh, I can make it myself!
Feather, blink root, deathweed, and fire blossom. I can make actual wings.
Soul of flight.
Soul of light, hmm.
Soul of night.
Okay. Well, Dylan, how about bouncy glow sticks? Sticky glow sticks?
What about this? Cell phone!
Displays everything. Allows you to return home at will?
Wait! Requires a PDA. How do I get a PDA?
What is this stuff? Oh my god, is that a constellation of a bunny?
Dude, we don't have room for this.
Ah, wait. What do you think of that? Haha! You like that?
I know you like it. You love it. Let's put a... let's put a chest here, I guess. Because why not?
Mayas will do it. Banners go in here. No, no, no, no, no. There.
See, it's a mess. I have to click on all the things. It's not good. It's bad.
Put this stuff in here. The skyward door. This golf feather.
I believe that goes in here. Cloud wall is also construction. Okay.
Fast. Stays with me. This stays with me. And the hunter potion. Yep, now we're ready again.
Let's move. Let's go! Come on, people! I have a whole entourage here.
Look at me optimizing this shit out of this game.
So there's actually something down here. Oh, that just connects. Okay.
I think I may... oh, you know what? It's night! Let's go to the old man.
It's time to fuck him up. Now that we have all the upgrades in the world,
let's go, people! What's that?
Oh, wait. Meteor. I forgot about that. There's a meteor somewhere, right? Meteor head.
Meteor head. Is that saying it's close, maybe? What is that?
Deathweed. Okay, they're coming from over here. They sound like fireworks when they die.
Wait. Oh, wait. Am I burning? Oh, I was burning! I didn't look at my HP. I'm a goddamn idiot. Holy
shit. Wow. Oh, no. Okay, remember, first death doesn't count. First death doesn't count.
Just saying. Just saying. Everyone knows it. It's not something I made up just now. It's real.
That was kind of a fail there. The funny thing is, I was looking in the top left trying to read
the description of that, and then I immediately went like, oh, it does that damage. And I looked
to the right, and I had like one heart left when I looked, and then I died.
Very unfortunate. Okay.
Zombies. Well, wait, I forgot to summon Abigail. I don't want to go back.
Rip Abigail. Honestly, she's kind of annoying anyway. Always making noise, fighting enemies.
I prefer no Abigail. Look at these meteor hits. Let's not die to this now again.
Oh yeah, dude. I wonder if I can damage it with this. Yeah, it's fine.
Whoa, we take a lot of damage quickly. Oh, you know what? This is my time to shine.
Fuck. Get away from me. Is this gonna work? No.
Poof. Bro, these... Oh, wait, I'm dying again. I'm not noticing. Holy shit.
I need to be careful here. It doesn't give me an indicator when I take damage. It's so weird.
Like, it's very stealthy damage you take there.
Okay, nice. Gaining some HP back. I'm gonna wait a bit here. Just gonna wait a bit.
I actually... wait, these things... let's test something real quick.
Yeah, they move straight through. Shit. All right, well... full HP. Let's go.
As long as I'm standing on something good, it's fine. Shoot him out of the sky.
Nice. I'm getting all this media right.
Wait, I'm taking damage again. How am I taking damage?
Wait, am I taking damage right now? Why did I take damage just now? I don't get it.
Oh, wait, what? I love this. Stop taking damage. The sound effect of shooting
these things down is nice.
Meteor... meteor head. Banner. Bro, hell yeah. Oh, one shot! Oops, careful. Oh, that's such a boon.
That's... oh, wait, wait, whoa! I took a bunch of damage again.
Wait, do I take damage if I'm close to it? Wait, I'm taking damage right now!
Oh, it's because I'm burning. I get it, I get it.
It's almost a one shot. Okay, just don't get hit by it. Easiest set done, of course.
Oh, that was stupid.
Ah, shit. Please get away from me.
Man, the automatic mining thing here is kind of dangerous sometimes.
This is actually a great spot to be in.
Get rid of all of this. Hang the banner again. There. I'm so focused right now.
It's so satisfying killing these things. Damn! I kind of... oops. I really just want to blow all this
shit up. I hate when they come from below because I can't hit them and I have to wait for them to
come close. Very annoying. Let me try with the... do I not have... do I not have... oh wait, I actually
do have some grenades. Oh, shit! Give me all that money. I need to craft more bombs. I've already
Ah! Please! How do I remove that? Why can't I remove that? What is happening? What? Do I need this?
I'm so confused. Okay, that makes more sense. But you can't remove the block underneath it, it seems.
Okay. I'm getting a lot of meteorite here.
Crimson block. Just keep mining. Yep, I'm getting all of this. I don't know if I need this much, but
I feel like this is something pretty significant, right?
I really wish I could stop these things from spawning. Maybe I just need to get rid of all
this meteorite, then they will actually stop spawning. Rid of it. Make a safe path. Oh god.
Oh no, I'm burning. It's fine. It's fine. Everything's fine. Oh, you know what? Maybe the water gun
would be great against these. I just don't have it on me right now.
Oh god. They sneak up on you. Even though you see them, they sort of still
manage to just sneak on you. Oh, okay, that's dangerous. Don't let that fall on you.
Okay. Whew, there's still a lot to go. How much do I have?
Uh, sort inventory. 200.
Wait, exactly 200? Or is this capped at 200? Hold on.
This is a bit of two of a suspicious number right now.
Okay, yeah. We can definitely get more. But here's the thing. I'm going to keep this here for now.
And I'm going to move on. I'm going to come back here if I ever need more.
I don't want to mind that anymore right now. Hopefully they're not going to
disturb me while I'm dealing with the old man. Oh wait, it's actually day now anyway.
Ah, shit. Maybe I will mine until it's night. Sure. Let's mine until it's night.
I would love to have some minions right now that could just take care of these.
Actually, hold on. I'm going to go back. I have an idea.
First I'm going to talk to Dylan. Dylan, tell me what I can do with this.
Meteorite Bar. Right. Okay, let's do that. Beautiful. Hey Dylan, what can I do with the Meteorite Bar?
Here we go. Meteor Hamax.
Space Gun.
Uses mana. Star Cannon.
Mini Shark. Oh yeah, right. Hold on.
Who sold that?
What's it? Dante. Hey, this isn't a movie, pal. Yeah, fine.
I think I have enough. I don't have enough.
Wait a minute. How much do I have in the old piggy bank?
Do we need to break open that piggy bank? Oh, here it is.
Ah, shit. I don't have enough.
Crap. Um, okay. Dylan, talk to me about these again.
Phase Blade. I can totally make one of these.
Meteors. Tell me these are not better. Nice, I have better ones.
Drill Containment Unit. Summons a writable drill? What?
Okay, never mind. This needs a shit ton of things.
God.
I think I want to try and make one of these Phase Blades.
It's going to require some of those gems. I have sapphires.
And what do I need? What station do I need?
Oh, wait.
Animal. Awesome.
Let's see here. Blue Phase Blade.
Sure. I need to see this.
Exactly as you would expect.
That's freaking awesome.
Maybe I can use that later to upgrade it somehow. I could also make...
What can I also make? I can actually make this. I think I made this before.
Let me actually test something real quick. We're doing a quick test.
Wait, how did I...
How did I equip this?
Where's my current hook? What? Hold on. Where is my hook?
Okay, whoops. Nope. What? No! Exit! Okay. Bro, where? How the fuck?
Oh! It looked like there was nothing in here because it blends in.
Okay, hold on. Actually, I want to do a quick test.
Is that longer? Wait a minute. It actually is. Why doesn't it say that?
Motherfucker. Why doesn't it say that?
Got... Okay, so what? They want me to just craft one of each color to test which one is the longest?
That doesn't make any fucking sense. Really?
See, now I'm starting to wonder what other effects items have if there's nothing written on it.
Oh, no!
Put that in there. How do I make bombs, actually? I need to remember how to make pure bombs.
Third bomb requires just a... ah, right.
Wait, meteor shot. Oh, that's only eight. I have no clue how I make bombs.
Yeah.
Bombs, bombs, bombs. Hmm. I mean, maybe he told me once.
How am I supposed to remember? Lead?
You know what? I have an idea. I have an idea. We're gonna do something drastic here.
Something very drastic. What's that? Shadewood?
Delete that.
Potions.
And grenades. Put that in here. No. Here. This is like, uh, Usables.
Third block. Okay. Sapphire.
Michelin. What did I... I guess in here. Yeah, I also have amethyst and stuff like that.
So what I want to do now is this.
Sword inventory. And then we're gonna just say...
Ah, wrong button. Loodle. Loot everything. And now we go down here and check out what we can make,
basically. We're just gonna walk around until we hopefully hit something correct.
Just gonna craft everything we can. Damn.
Cryptane. Why would I do that? It doesn't sound good. Clay pot.
Okay, that's it for there. Let me go a little bit to the left now.
Okay, let's see. Here. I can make all of this. Throwing knives.
You know what? Let's make one of these to give to, uh...
Oh. I wonder if this is a multiplayer thing. Capture the gem. You know, you can kill each other
in whoever has the gem, whatever. But we can apparently use it as a material, so we can try that,
I guess. Magi-luminescence. Increases movement speed and acceleration. Provides light when,
holy shit, that seems insanely good. I'll make that. Fleeting. Let's try and put that there
instead. Let's see, how fast are we? Let me put it off. Oh yeah, look. Acceleration. Super slow.
Noon. Oh, that's so good. That's a great item. Fuck yeah. Tin helmet? No, thanks.
What else should I make? See, amethyst? I don't know if I should make that. Maybe it's better,
maybe not. Should I just fucking try everything? Space- what's that? Helmet.
There's nothing else here, right? Again? Here they come again.
So now I want to go up here and go like this and deposit all. We take the next chest.
Loot all. And now we see what we can craft now. I need to close off this door here.
Of course I don't have to make materials for it. Oh, these spiky balls suck.
They're not that great, are they? I'm gonna sell them. Here, you can have that. That's right.
I can make a mushroom campfire. Please keep me alone.
Okay, I'm gonna close this off. This blood moon is very, very... why is this
chest glowing? Oh, it's just a little effect on it, I think.
Instruction. Give me dirt block. Block it off. We're also gonna block the other side.
How come they're not getting in here? That's actually kind of curious.
I wonder if it's because of the little...
Hold on. We're gonna do a test. What if I go like this? Is that really tripping them up?
Then again, there's no ground enemies, so maybe that's why I actually... oh wait, here it comes.
Let's see. Yeah, look. They can't get in. Fucking idiots. Idiots!
Let me just put this here for now. Close the door. Have fun. Wait, how did you get in?
Maybe it doesn't work like I think it does. Unless the door was open. Let's see.
Yeah, they still managed to get in. Okay, never mind. Fuck off.
Wow, he gets confused. Hold on, let me move more of this, actually.
Uh, I just want to craft right now. I have defeated the 50th dribbler.
Apparently. Uh, craft. What can I make?
Yeah, they get inside. I have to dirt wall that shit.
What's that? Wait, dribbler banner? Why is it so small?
Oh, wait, is it because... oh, I see.
I get it. I get it. Okay, craft. Finally, I can craft in peace now.
Cactus sword.
Mushroom wall. I'm looking for a special chest.
Seaf, yeah.
I'll have that. Honestly, don't make it out of everything.
Ball of soup.
Bamboo door. What's this?
Bath top. Dresser. Cactus toilet. Cactus toilet?
Yeah, I don't know about that. It seems like a really bad idea. You know, actually,
I just realized maybe I need lead for this. Chests, right? Give me that.
Finally. Okay, let me remove this. Bam. Let's make two bamboo chests. Lovely. And let's make...
What else can I make? What else can I make? Cactus chest. Two of those.
Uh, just have it in the hand, I guess. Look at that. Beautiful.
Then we're going to sort it later. Organics, deposit all. And then, no, take the lead.
Michelinius. Tegel. This is such a cumbersome system, I gotta be honest, dude. This is rough,
dude. This crafting system right here. I feel like it's not thought through very well.
Great. No, that's a great. Not a crate. I keep making that mistake. Shit.
Here. Can I make anything here? You know, anything is... Maybe there's combinations
between the chests that I can't. All right, fine. I guess Michelinius, deposit all.
But I do need this construction. Now we take all this, because this is gonna
allow us to do all kinds of shit, I think. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Shadewood chests. Two of those. Thank you.
And then we're gonna... I think all of this is gonna get way better when I
somehow get a proper organization going. Yeah. Construction, deposit all.
What else can I do? I also have some organics here. Look at all these.
Oh, give me those bars again. Nothing, it seems. Deposit all. Okay. Give me that.
Put it in. Actually, bring this to Dylan. Let's just quickly test.
Sapphire mine cart.
See, this is probably faster than the normal mine cart, but I wouldn't know.
I don't know. I don't know. Maybe it is. Maybe it is. Put it in here.
Michelinius. Also summon Abigail. This could be useful to just have on. You know what? I'm
gonna have to experiment with the void storage shit, because maybe that's the solution to my issues.
Maybe I want to get rid of this for now and use this instead.
Yeah, seems good. Okay. What do I want to do next? I have a lens, actually. Throw that in the chest.
Now. Hold on. Didn't I make some chests just now? What did I put them?
Money trough. Someone's flying. Where did I get that?
Huh? Wait, what? Someone's flying. Wait.
What if I do... Hold on a second. Where did I get that?
Where did you come from? Bro, I'm so confused right now. Let's do a test here. Put this in here.
See ya. Oh, that's gonna be so much better. I am so happy. Why did I get that? I have
no clue, dude. Oh, that's a nice feature, at least. It actually just replaces the chests.
Look. God, I'm so happy about that. That's lovely. So now I can replace these with the organics.
Fantastic feature. See, I like that. That's great.
Oh, that's a great one. Put that there for now.
Sunflower. I need to check all of my items, I guess.
So these two chests here are going to become my weapons and utility and armor and all that.
Weapons and utility on top, and armor and equipables on the bottom. That's the plan right now. Take all.
Yep. And then inside of here, let's take... let's sort this.
Oh wait, I should probably deposit this somewhere. Let's have a chest
for ores and stuff. That could be these two over here.
Deposit all. And take the things that do not fit, because there's more that fit than do not fit.
Sort. For example, that is in there and that is in there. This is in there and that is in there. Sort again.
Give me that, give me that, give me that. The sorting does help a lot, actually. Just get a quick,
you know, what sticks out here is your sample. Okay, good. And then
that's a good start. Construction. Here we're going to put some... let me take a sort.
All these, non-mower.
This one can be destroyed because it sucks now that I have a better one.
I want the... oh, why did I just... I have an idea. I have some duplic... wasn't there something to do with this?
How do I... hold on, can I maybe speak to... where are you at? Fiel? Was it you?
Goblin thieves aren't very good at their job. They can't even steal from an unlocked chest.
Reforge. Annoying undertaker. I don't want to do that. I want to use this.
How does this work? This clearly had a function, didn't it? I could have... oh wait, I have an idea.
I can actually pick it up. Allows the combining of some accessories. Okay, some accessories.
How, though? Let me put it somewhere else. Maybe it needs to be close to a crafting table or something?
I would expect that to be a little window here, similar to the... hats over here.
I don't get it. I don't get it. Let me actually put these here.
I'll rip them off my inventory. Get them out. Get them out.
Let's put some chests randomly. Just decorative chests. Sure.
Why not? Let's get them out of the inventory.
Okay, weapons up here. Let's put these back in for now.
And this is going to be armor and equipables.
Sword items. Sword.
Put these in there. These are all... oh, this is an equipable.
Sword. Oh, these are melee. These are ranged. And this is... oh.
And this is spells. That's nice, actually. That it does it like that.
But I guess this can also go in here. Maybe I can use it later.
Actually, I can't. It's not in a material, so that will be sold.
This goes in here. Piggybank goes back down. Put it on the dresser there.
Let's see. In. Lucky horse. Oh, actually. Let's put them here.
Different loadout, right?
This sucks.
Yo, this is actually sick. You switch loadout? Take no fall damage. Switch back.
Maybe we can have a mobility loadout.
What is this? Guide to plant fiber cord.
It allows the connection of vine rope from vines. This plays depth.
It takes enemies. But then again, these are materials, so...
Hmm. Actually, I'm going to keep it simple here.
Oops. What? Hailey! Fuck off! Thank you.
Put them in. And this one... Is that... That's more like a utility.
There. This one, too. No, actually, I'm selling this one.
I can't wait to have this all fucking fixed. The whole inventory situation is going to be great.
Comes a baby face. I don't want that.
I don't want it.
There's a counterweight.
This one right here is insanity. I have no idea where I got it or how it ended up in my chest.
But boy am I glad I spotted that.
Dang. Okay.
I think that's enough inventory management for now.
I don't want to heal.
Shop. Take this pickaxe, please.
Dive at. No.
Would you actually sell, Hailey, anything useful?
Holy shit!
Kites can be flown on windy days.
Whoa, hold on. Dog license?
Use to adopt a dog for your town.
Use additional licenses to activate the pet exchange program.
And a leather whip. Your summons will focus.
Struck enemies. Die, monster.
Grab a lot of trees like a...
Okay, you know what? I'm saving money, though.
I'm saving money for the minigun.
Don't spend money. I'm saving it.
I want the minigun.
Help. I hear a raise of lizard men live in the jungle.
Maybe you can get the attention of one by felling a giant beast of the jungle.
Say no more, fam. I'm your man.
Also, switch back to that.
What did I just do?
I heard a sound just now.
Anyway, put that there. Magic mirror here.
These are my main utility things I will use.
Let's do that.
Glow sticks.
Golden key. I don't know when I'll get to use that.
Anyway, the plan is to go see an old man.
Very soon.
Oh, no.
Put it back. There we go.
All right. What is the time anyway?
Okay, yeah, I actually got to get going.
I have a deal with someone.
So let's just engage the old printer.
Oh, holy shit.
I just got a bunch of items there.
Let me sort this in there.
All right. Finally, we have some inventory management here going.
Even though it's not perfect yet, it's becoming perfect.
Also, hold on. Am I just realizing?
Oh, I don't need these.
They hang on the wall.
I looked at that. Hold on.
Wait a minute. That doesn't look quite right.
Awesome. That actually makes me happy that I just saw that.
Okay, that's it for now.
Save and exit.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Guys, this game is fun and I may be a little addicted.
So I played way too much of this game lately.
I need to calm it down a bit, especially next week.
I have some work to do.
I can't be playing this game as much as I have already.
I need to tone it down a bit.
So I'm going to try to restrict streams to about three hours,
maybe a little less. We'll see.
But I definitely have a craving for the Terraria right now.
But I got to go.
So all I want to do is quickly do a smooth transition here
and say Kratus.
Welcome to the potato. I see you there.
I don't know if you're still here, but if you are, thank you for joining.
It's so cool.
Everyone, thanks for watching and having fun watching me struggle through this.
I know it's painful at times. I get it. Trust me.
It's also painful for me.
But I hope you'll forgive me and trust me that I will figure things out in time.
Like always.
Thanks for watching.
You guys are the best.
I'll see you guys later.
Have a good one.
Adios.